BU Records: Retired Professors and Administrators Program, Inclusive: 1947-2020, undated, Bulk:1984-2017
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
BU Records: Retired Professors and Administrators Program
Inclusive: 1947-2020, undated, Bulk:1984-2017
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
BU/312
Baylor Retired Professors/ Administrators Center
26 document boxes
BU Records: Retired Professors and Administrators Program contains correspondence, faculty information and obituaries, newsletters, and other materials from the program's efforts to connect, engage, and honor the legacy of retired faculty and administrators.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Excellent.
Biography/Profile
In 1972, the Baylor Chapter of the American Association of University Professors conducted a survey of recent Baylor retirees to gauge their interest in a Baylor retirement organization. Upon hearing back from respondents that such a program would be helpful, Baylor University Executive Vice President and Provost Herbert H. Reynolds, later President of Baylor University, authorized the creation of what was called at the time the Baylor Retired Professor's Center. With veteran professor and administrator P.D. Browne as the first director, the center began contacting past Baylor professors and administrators and keeping in touch with them through regular mailings of newsletters, campus newspapers, and other materials produced by the university.
By 1977, the program was called the Retired Professors Program, and had 97 members, 77 of whom still lived in Waco close to the university campus. Browne, as director, conducted an annual retirement luncheon for new retirees, where retiring faculty and staff were presented with plaques or certificates at a formal lunch. P.D. Browne retired as director in 1982.
Dr. Floyd Davidson was appointed as the new director in 1983 and led the department for the next six years. During that time, membership continued to grow. Dr. W.J. Wimpee, former professor of Religion, next led the department, 1990-1998. By 1998, when Dr. Rufus Spain began as director, membership was more than 600, and the department was coordinating a monthly newsletter, regular luncheons, flowers for shut-ins, hospital visits to members as necessary, and various other functions. William J. Dube III next became Director of the Retired Professors and Administrators Program, together with his duties as Senior Director of Stewardship in the University Development department at Baylor. It was probably at this time that the Retired Professors and Administrators Program became a division of the Development office at Baylor.
The Retired Professors and Administrators Program continues to provide opportunities to serve, connect, and explore for the community of retired Baylor professors and administrators.
Scope and Content
The BU Records: Retired Professors and Administrators Program contains a variety of materials from the Retired Professors and Administrators Program. Materials in the collection represent a continuum over the time the program has existed, with no major gaps of time present. Series I, Administrative, contains business correspondence, membership lists, luncheon planning information, budget data, and other materials. Series II: Biographical and Obituaries, includes both obituaries and information kept by the Retired Professors and Administrators Program office on members. Series III, Newsletters, contains the newsletters produced by the Retired Professors and Administrators Program for the benefit of members. The long-running newsletters, usually two pages, contain obituaries, reminisces of professors and events, and other information about Baylor and Waco.
Arrangement
BU Records: Retired Professors and Administrators Program was arranged in two groups at the time of this finding aid: one group of older records that was still in original order from the time of donation and a group of newer records donated recently that had been refoldered. Both groups of materials were integrated into the new current series arrangement.
Currently, the BU Records: Retired Professors and Administrators Program is arranged in three series: I. Administrative, II. Newsletters, and Biographical and Obituaries.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. BU/312. Acquired 1997-00-00
Related Resources
Related references
"About." Retired Professors and Administrators Program. Accessed 2020 September 18.
"Baylor Begins Program for Retiring Professors." Waco Citizen. 1974 January 10. Accessed 2020 September 18.
"Baylor Does Something for Retirees." Mexia Daily News. 1974 January 22. Accessed 2020 September 18.
"Baylor 'Founders' Day." Waco Citizen. 1982 January 29. Accessed 2020 September 18.
"Baylor University Luncheon To Honor Retiring Personnel." Waco Citizen. 1977 April 29. Accessed 2020 September 18.
"Continuing a Commitment to Retirees." Baylor Magazine. 2013 Spring. Accessed 2020 September 18.
"HOF Winners 2019: Bill Dube." Baylor Line Foundation. 2019 April 26. Accessed 2020 September 18.
"Philip Browne Guest Speaker for Lydia McLane." Mexia Daily News. 1975 December 17. Accessed 2020 September 18.
"Retired Professors/Administrators Program Honors Rufus Spain and Welcomes New Director." Baylor News Online. Accessed 2020 September 18.
"Retired Professors Awards Luncheon." Waco Citizen. 1989 May 2. Accessed 2020 September 18.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
Baylor University -- Faculty.; Baylor University -- History -- 20th century.; Baylor University Retired Professors/Administrators Program.
Genres
Business correspondence.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Newsletters.; Obituaries.
- Administrative, 1972-2009, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Excellent.
  Biography/Profile
  This series contains budgets, correspondence, luncheon planning documents, and other materials related with running the Retired Professors and Administrators Program. This series is in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Compact disk (CD); Floppy disk; Video home system (VHS) tapes
  - Correspondence, From President Reynolds (1 of 3), 1973-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, From President Reynolds (2 of 3), 1973-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, From President Reynolds (3 of 3), 1973-1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Approval from President Reynolds, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Ioda Mohr White (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Ioda Mohr White (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Retired Professors, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Retired Professors, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letters to the President, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Appointments and Congratulations (1 of 3), 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Appointments and Congratulations (2 of 3), 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Appointments and Congratulations (3 of 3), 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - House of Poetry, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Retiree of the Year, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Address Selection, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Personnel Nearing Retirement (1 of 2), 1986-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Personnel Nearing Retirement (2 of 2), 1986-2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Notes, P.D. Browne, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Retirement Eligibility, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Retirement Eligibility, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Retirement Eligibility, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Membership Requirements (1 of 6), 1972-2008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Membership Requirements (2 of 6), 1972-2008 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Membership Requirements (3 of 6), 1972-2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Membership Requirements (4 of 6), 1972-2008 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Membership Requirements (5 of 6), 1972-2008 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Membership Requirements (6 of 6), 1972-2008 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Membership Roster, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Membership Roster, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Retirement Data, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Retirees (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Retirees (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Retirees (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Retirees (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Retirees, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Retirees (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Retirees (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Retirees (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Retirees (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Birthdays, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - P.D.’s Corner, 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Catering Manual, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Retired Professors Handbook, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Names for Retired Professors Handbook, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Sample Retirement Handbook, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Retirees Receiving the Lariat, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Trustees Receiving the Lariat, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Introduction for Charles Barrow, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Sternberg Lectures, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Founders Day Celebration, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Chapel Forum Speakers, 1970-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Plaque Awards (1 of 4), 1974-1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Plaque Awards (2 of 4), 1974-1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Plaque Awards (3 of 4), 1974-1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Plaque Awards (4 of 4), 1974-1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Director’s Remarks at Luncheon, 1983-1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Luncheons and Visitation Expenses (1 of 2), 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Luncheons and Visitation Expenses (2 of 2), 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Luncheon, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Tributes to Ray Summers by W.J. Wimpee, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - American-Thai Christian Foundation (1 of 2), 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - American-Thai Christian Foundation (2 of 2), 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Southern Baptist Convention, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Computer Information, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Results of Questionnaire University Program for Retirees, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Seal and Newsletter Headings, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Gilmore, Joseph L., 1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Baptist General Convention of Texas—Southern Baptist Convention, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Summer Enrollment, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Luncheon Reservations, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - First Families of Baylor Award (1 of 2), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - First Families of Baylor Award (2 of 2), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Award Plaques and Certificates (1 of 2), 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Award Plaques and Certificates (2 of 2), 1974-1984 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Changes to Group Health Insurance, 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Nearing Retirement and Publications, 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Reynolds Summer School for Retirees, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Yonok College (1 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Yonok College (2 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Yonok College Publications (1 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Yonok College Publications (2 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Yonok College, Photographs, circa 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hong Kong Baptist College Newsletters, 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Bell, Robert. “Is Retirement for You?” Modern Maturity, 1976 October-November (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Patsy Hollandsworth Estate (1 of 2), 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Patsy Hollandsworth Estate (2 of 2), 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - History, 1974-2013 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Associate Members, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Budget, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 2009-2010 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Budget, 2010-2011 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Budget, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Budget, 2018-2019 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Macebearers for Graduation (1 of 4), 2010-2015 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Macebearers for Graduation (2 of 4), 2010-2015 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Macebearers for Graduation (3 of 4), 2010-2015 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Macebearers for Graduation (4 of 4), 2010-2015 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Committee, 1999-2012 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - History, 1972-2006 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Benefits, 2002-2017 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Directory, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Directory, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Index, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - General Photographs (1 of 3), undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - General Photographs (2 of 3), undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - General Photographs (3 of 3), undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Portrait Photographs (1 of 2), undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Portrait Photographs (2 of 2), undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Group Photographs, circa 1972 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 3), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 3), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook (3 of 3), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Retiree Lists, Zip Drive, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Retiree Photographs, Compact Disk, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, Compact Disk, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Luncheon, VHS video tape, 2002 January 22 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Newsletters, 1983-1994; 2
  This series contains newsletters generated over the time of several different directors. The newsletters provided updates on Baylor events and initiatives, upcoming events hosted by the Retired Professors and Administrators Program, and reminisces from past times at Baylor. Director P.D. Browne wrote many of the articles about Baylor history and leaders from the 1930s-1960s. This series is in excellent condition.
  - Newsletters, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Current Newsletter, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Guest Column (1 of 2), 1988 — 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Guest Column (2 of 2), 1988 - 1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Biographical and Obituaries, 1947-2020, undated; 3
  This series contains biographical and obituary materials, including member files kept for reference by the office. This series is in good condition.
  - Abercrombie, Rita, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Abrahams, Mary, 2017 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Achor, Joseph, 2016-2017 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Adams, Bill, 1984-2014 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Adams, Linda, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Adams, Mary L., 2011-2016 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Adams, Sudie M., 1986-2011 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Adams, William (Floyd), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Airaudi, Jesse T., 2014 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Alcorn, Suzanne, 2002-2009 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Aldredge, Gwendolyn, 2002-2017 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Alexander, W. Merle, 1994-2006 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Allen, A. Dale, 2002-2017 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Allen, Stephanie, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Allen, Robert T., 2008-2014 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Amsler, Margaret, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Anderson, Eddie, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Andrews, Robert O. and Lucille H., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Ard, Michael, 2001-2010 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Armistead, Paul, 2002-2016 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Armstrong, Chole, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Arnold, David, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Arredondo, Patricia, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Aslanian, Richard, 2005-2017 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Atkins, Richard L., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Avant, Gayle, 2010-2011 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Backus, Carolyn, 2006-2008 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Baier, Margaret E., 2014-2016 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Bailey, Donald, 2008-2012 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Baird, Robert “Bob”, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Baker, Anita, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Baker, Anna Ree, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Baker, Betty Ruth, 2016 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Baker, Eugene W., 1999-2010 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Baker, Lisa, 2017 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Baker, Martha, 1998-2014 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Baker, Mary Louise, 2010-2014 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Baker, Melvin C., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Baker, William G., 2011-2014 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Bailey, Anne Lowery, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Baldridge, Robert, 2020 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Barcus, James, 2016 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Barkema, Martha, 1984-1999 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Lewis, Barker, 2006-2014 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Bargainer, James, 1979-2009 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Barnett, Madalene, 1995-2015 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Barr, Norma, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Barrett, Elden, 2011-2015 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Barrow, Sugie, 1984-2015 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Bartlett, Thomas, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Bartoli, Lino, 2000-2004 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Bartosch, Joseph R., 1999 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Basden, Edward, 2017 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Battles, Mary Helen, 2009-2014 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Bayer, John W., 2000 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Beaver, Harold, 1998-2014 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Beckenhauer, Jaylie, 2016 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Beckner, Weldon E., 2006-2012 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Belew, John S., 1992-2017 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Bell, Carolyn, 2002-2017 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Bellegie, Nick (N. J.), 2000-2005 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Benedict, Helen E., 2014 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Bennett, Barbara, 2000-2014 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Berres, Jean L., 2003-2010 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Berry, Don, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Berry, Stephanie, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Berryhill, James, 2004-2018 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Bianchi, Elizabeth G., 2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Bice, Noley, 2017 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Biles, Raymond, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Bishop, Michael, 2005-2011 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Black, Olive, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Black, Sadie Jo, 1998-2017 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Blackmon, Gary, 2005-2011 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Bohannon, Tom, 2007-2010 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Bond, Edith G., 2009 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Boone, Hal, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Booras, Mary, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Boswell, William J., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Browne, Philip Dale, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Bowen, Adair, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Bowman, Judy, 2010-2015 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Boyd, John H., 2011 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Brabham, Daniel, 2017 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Bracken Thelma D., 1996-2004 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Bradley, Walter, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Branyon, Joan, 2000-2017 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Bratcher, Nancy, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Breckenridge, James, 1998-2013 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Breithaupt, Charlotte, 2004-2009 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Bright, Robert E., 1997-2016 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Bronaugh, Richmond, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Brooks, Gary, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Brooks, Roger, 1998-2016 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Broom, H. N., 1992-2006 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Brown, Bryce C., 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Brown, Ellen, 2010-2014 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Brown, Lyle C., 1998-2017 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Brown, Slyvia D., 2020 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Brown, William G., 1999-2018 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Browne, Diana, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Budd, Charlene S., 2005-2009 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bufton, Karen, 2016 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Burchette, Ray, 1999-2014 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Burckhardt, Jochem Fritz, 1969-1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Burkett, Helen, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Burkett, Sally, 1968-1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Burleson, Blake, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Burgess, Cynthia, 2017 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Burns, Scott, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Busby, James E., 2002-2016 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Busch, Kenneth, 2009-2020 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Butler, Barbara, 2006-2012 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Cadwallader, Chester S., undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Cagle, Louise, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Cain, Patricia Ann, 2011-2017 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Callan, Jerrie D., 2016 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Campbell, Dave, 2011-2012 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Campbell, Richard, 2017 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Cannata, Sam and Ginny, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Cannon, Berta Lee, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Cannon, Raymond J., 2013-2017 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Capp, Glen, 1992-2009 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Carpenter, Walter J., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Carroll, Eulalie T., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Casey, Jean, 2000-2013 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Caskey, Mrs. J., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Cassell, Michael, 2008-2015 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Castello, Sherry B., 1998-2015 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Caston, Ellie, 2016 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Charlton, Thomas L., 2010-2012 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Cheavens, Alice, 1993-2000 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Cherry, Robert Foster, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Chesser, Delton L., 2009-2017 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Chewning, Richard C., 2000-2015 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Chonko, Larry, 2007-2012 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Christian, C. Wallace, 1998-2017 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Cobbs, Linda, 2009-2012 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Cockerell, Leone, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Coker, Dolores Muga, 1975-1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Coldiron, Jack, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cole, James, 1998-2014 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cole, Mabel Lynn, 2009-2011 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Coleman, Mary, 1986-1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Coley, Kenneth, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Collins, Lane, 2005-2012 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Collmer, Robert, 1998-2015 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Colvin, Herbert, 2005-2015 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Conaway, Betty, 2016 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Coody, Jerry, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cook, Alan N., 2003-2020 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cook, Carol Ann, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Cook, Gary, 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Cook, JoAnn, 2006-2014 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Cook, Patricia, 1963-1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Cooper, William F., 2003-2020 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Copeland, Mable, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Corbin, Linda S., 2005 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Cornelius, Roy, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Corley, Julie, 2013-2014 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Couey, Richard, 2007-2012 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Cox, Estaline, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Cox, Linda, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Creasey, Jimmy, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Cresson, Bruce, 2000-2010 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Criswell, W.A., 1992 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Crow, Douglas W., 2003-2017 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Crowder, Lenora, 1998-2010 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Crump, Steve, 1999-2013 (Box 12, Folder 30)